Guide to the American Planning Association records, 1925-2015.
American Planning Association records,
- Paul Farmer Files
  - Alphabetical File
    - Oregon's Future' - Newsletter - Spring 2001 (Box 150, Folder 60)
    - Governance Survey, 2002 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Government Law Center, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Growing Smart Legislative Project & Guidebook, 2001-2002 (Box 151, Folder 3)
      Correspondence, Printed Materials
    - Growing Smart Legislative Project & Guidebook, 2001 (Box 151, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, Draft
    - Growth Management Issues, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Hercules District Plan, 2000 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Hardy Holzman Pfeiffer Association (HHPA), 2004 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - High School Essay Contest - Essays, 2008 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Housing - Printed Materials, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Housing - Report 'Housing Choice Voiucher Location Patterns', 2003 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - ICLEI (Local governments for sustainability), 2010 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - International City/County Management Association (ICMA), 2003 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Interior Design for APA Office Chicago - Drawings by Torchia, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - International - CHINA, 2002 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - International Code Council, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - International Downtown Association, 2002, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Initiatives APA/AICP should undertake, 2001 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Institute for building and home safety - Printed materials, 2002 (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Institute for Justice, 2002 (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - JAPA (Journal of the American planning Association) - Proposals, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - JAPA-VT (Virginia Tech), 2004; CD - 2316 (Box 151, Folder 21-23)
    - JAPA - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 151, Folder 23)
    - JFK School Conference - Printed Materials, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 24)
    - Kennedy School (Harvard), 2003 (Box 151, Folder 25-26)
    - Institute of Transportation Engineers (ITE) - Constitution, 2001 (Box 151, Folder 27)
    - Sir Terry Farrell Lecture - Press release from the Royal Town Planning Institute, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 28)
    - Job searches, 2002, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 29)
    - Judith McManus Price Scholarship, 2002 (Box 151, Folder 30)
    - Knowledgeplex - Printed Materials, 2001 (Box 151, Folder 31)
    - Judy Neel Associates, 2002 (Box 151, Folder 32)
    - Korean Planners Association - Speaker Bruce Knight, 2009 (Box 151, Folder 33)
    - Bruce Knight's address to Korean Planners Association, 2009; DVD-1426-1427 (Box 151, Folder 34)
    - Lambda Alpha International - Documents, Newsletters 'KeyNotes', 2002-2005 (Box 151, Folder 34)
    - Landslide hazards & planning - Report, 2000 (Box 151, Folder 35)
    - International Planning Activities, 2000 (Box 151, Folder 36)
    - International Federation for Housing & Planning - Publications, 2001-2003 (Box 151, Folder 37-38)
    - Land Use Law and Zoning Digest - Correspondence, Memos, Budgets, 1991-2004 (Box 151, Folder 39)
    - Land Use Law and Zoning Digest -Newsletters, Marketing proposals, 2001, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 40)
    - Land Use Law and Zoning Digest- Marketing and Branding, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 41)
    - Land Use Law and Zoning Digest- Marketing and Branding, 2000 (Box 151, Folder 42)
    - Leadership Plenty Training Program - Correspondence, memos, 2002-2003 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - L'Enfant Lectures, 2005-2008 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - APA/National Building Museum (NBM) 2014 Agreement - Capital Council for the Built Environment Membership (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - APA Life Membership dues correspondence, 2004 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Lincoln Institute of Land Policy documents, 2002-2003 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC) - Correspondence, Newsletters, 2002, 2003 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Lower Manhattan, 2001, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Mailings, Memos, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Mandatory Continuing education, 2001 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Meeting of the Minds, 2008 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - McGuire Woods, 2007 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - National Association of Housing & Redevelopment Officials, 2006 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - National Association of Home Builders, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - National Association of Regional Councils, 2002, 2008 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - National building Museum - Correspondence, Memos, 2002 - 2006 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - National building Museum - Brochures, Annual Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - National Charrette Institute, 2003, 2004 (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - National Planning Conferences (Box 152, Folder 18-20)
      - Chicago, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 18)
      - Denver, 2003 (Box 152, Folder 19)
      - Washington DC, 2004 (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - National Transportation Safety Board, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - Neal Gerber Eisenberg, 2007 (Box 152, Folder 22)
    - James Nelson - EEOC Charges documents, 2003, 2009 (Box 152, Folder 23)
    - New York / New Visions - Working Draft, Undated (Box 152, Folder 24)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 2002-2004 (Box 152, Folder 25)
    - Planning Accreditation Board (PAB) (Box 152, Folder 26-46)
      - Bylaws, Correspondence, 2003, 2006, 2008 (Box 152, Folder 26)
      - Application for recognition, 2001 (Box 152, Folder 27)
      - Election Chair, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 28)
      - AICP Site visitor pool members, Undated (Box 152, Folder 29)
      - Committee Roster, 2006 (Box 152, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Memos, 2000-2004 (Box 152, Folder 31)
      - Proposals, Reports, 2003, 2004 (Box 152, Folder 32)
      - The Accreditation Document - Criteria and Procedures of the Planning Accreditation Process- Parts 1 & 2, 2006 (Box 152, Folder 33-34)
      - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, 2008 (Box 152, Folder 35)
      - Accreditation site visit documents- Forms, Manuals, Reports, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 36)
      - Clemson University Self-study report - Planning Degrees Accreditation Review - Parts 1-8, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 37-44)
      - Clemson University Planning Degrees Accreditation Review - Correspondence, Printed materials, 2002 (Box 152, Folder 45)
      - Clemson University Planning Degrees Accreditation Review - Site visit report, 2003 (Box 152, Folder 46)
    - Planning & Environmental Law, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - PERSI Project (Practice, Education, and Research for Sustainable Infrastructure), 2006 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Pew Partnership, 2002-2003 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Planning Agencies - Washington DC Office of Planning, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      Comprehensive and Action Plans
    - Planning Advisory Service Summit, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Planning Commissioner, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Planning Director's Mailing, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - MOU- Planning Institute, APA, Harvard, Lincoln Institute, Undated (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Planning Law Review - Survey, 2007 (Box 153, Folder 9-10)
    - Planetizen - Info for Attorneys, 2007, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - City of Preoria, 2005-2006 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - City of Preoria - Convention & Visitors Bureau, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Preserve America, 2003-2004 (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Property Rights, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - ProQuest Archive Agreement, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Proclamations, 1996-1999 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Public Administration Review - Issue (Volume 62), September 2002 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Qualifications, 1995, Undated (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - Renewable Natural Resources Foundation, 2002, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Retreat, 2001-2002 (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - Russia City Management, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Salary Survey (2004), 2003-2004 (Box 153, Folder 23)
    - Sea Grant - Illinois - Indiana, 1999, 2000 (Box 153, Folder 24)
    - Sierra Club, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 25)
    - Signs, 2002, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 26)
    - Smart Growth America, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - Smart Growth Network, 2001-2003 (Box 153, Folder 28)
    - SPUR -San Francisco Planning + Urban Resserach Association- Newsletters, documents, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 29)
    - Squire Sanders, 2007 (Box 153, Folder 30)
    - South African Planning Institute Conference, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 31)
    - STAR - Steering Committee - Conference Call, 2009 (Box 153, Folder 32)
    - State of Washington - Office of Communiyt Development, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 33)
    - Street Tree Seminar (Urban Forests), 2005 (Box 153, Folder 34)
    - Student Fellowships, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 35)
    - Subscriptions, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 36)
    - Super Topics- Housing, correspondence, documents, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 37)
    - Super Topics- Housing, Printed materials, 2002, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 38)
    - Transportation - Correspondence, Printed Materials, 2002-2003 (Box 153, Folder 39)
    - Transportation Research Board, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 40)
    - United Airlines, 2002, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 41)
    - United Nations, 2004-2006 (Box 153, Folder 42)
    - University of Arizona, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 43)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 44)
    - University of Illinois, Chicago, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 45)
    - University of Oregon - School of Architecture and Allied Arts - Board of visitors, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 46)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 47)
    - University of Wisconsin - Milwaukee, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 48)
    - Urban Land Institute, 2001-2004 (Box 153, Folder 49)
    - Urban Planning and Design standards - Advisory Board Meeting, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 50)
    - US Department of Housing and Urban Development, 2003-2004 (Box 153, Folder 51)
    - US Department of Interior, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 52)
    - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 53)
    - WEB: Committee documents, agendas, memos, 2001, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 54)
    - Wiley Project, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 55)
    - World Town Planning Day, 2001, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 56)
    - Zoning Ordinances, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, Documents, Newspaper Articles
    - Barber, Robert, 2000 (Box 153, Folder 58)
    - Branca, Steven, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 59)
    - Blue, Michael, 2002-2007 (Box 153, Folder 60)
    - Bunnell, Gene, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 61)
    - Cassella, Sam, 1993, 2001-2003 (Box 153, Folder 62)
    - Chandler, Michael, 1999 (Box 153, Folder 63)
    - Claus, James B., 2001 (Box 153, Folder 64)
    - Duncan, James B., 2002 (Box 153, Folder 65)
    - Easley, V. Gail, 1999 (Box 153, Folder 66)
    - Freund, Adrian P., 1999 (Box 153, Folder 67)
    - Gallas, Walter, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 68)
    - Gann, John L., Jr., 2004 (Box 153, Folder 69)
    - Garnett, Joanne E., 1997 (Box 153, Folder 70)
    - Gerckens, Laurence C., 1999, 2001 (Box 153, Folder 71)
    - Groh, Monica, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 72)
    - Harper, Michael A., 1997 (Box 153, Folder 73)
    - Heard, Isaac "Ike", 2006-2007 (Box 153, Folder 74)
    - Henderson, Janice, 2009 (Box 153, Folder 75)
    - Hollenbeck, Rion, Undated (Box 153, Folder 76)
    - Horsburgh, Patrick, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 77)
    - Hunter, Robert B., 2001-2003 (Box 153, Folder 78)
    - Jaffeson, Richard, 2007-2008 (Box 153, Folder 79)
    - Johnson, Mark (Schaumburg), 2003 (Box 153, Folder 80)
    - Kalkowski, Buzz, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 81)
    - Karetski, Al, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 82)
    - Kahn, Vivian, 1997, 2001 (Box 153, Folder 83)
    - Lagrange, Lucien, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 84)
    - Lauber, Dan, Undated (Box 153, Folder 85)
    - Lazar, Ellen W., 2003 (Box 153, Folder 86)
    - Leighton, Thomas, 2007 (Box 153, Folder 87)
    - Lucero, Lora, 2008, 2011 (Box 153, Folder 88)
    - McClendon, Bruce, 2000-2006 (Box 153, Folder 89)
    - McCracken, Laurin, 2007 (Box 153, Folder 90)
    - McGrath, Jr., Dorn, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 91)
    - Mitchell, Robert P., 1997, 2001 (Box 153, Folder 92)
    - More, Sarah, 1997 (Box 153, Folder 93)
    - Moussalli, Guy, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 94)
    - Peck, Mary Kay, 1997-2003 (Box 153, Folder 95)
    - Petrie, Pattsi, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 96)
    - Phillips, David, 2007 (Box 153, Folder 97)
    - Pratt, Sue E., 1997, 2001 (Box 153, Folder 98)
    - Preston, Steven, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 99)
    - Rossant, James, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 100)
    - Salkin, Patricia, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 101)
    - Schwartz, Sue, 1999-2003 (Box 153, Folder 102)
    - Sheffels, Patricia, Undated (Box 153, Folder 103)
    - Shepard, Nora, Undated (Box 153, Folder 104)
    - Siegel, Dave, 1999, 2006-2008 (Box 153, Folder 105)
    - Silver, Mitchell, 1999-2005 (Box 153, Folder 106)
    - Swayne, Carol, 1997 (Box 153, Folder 107)
    - Willmer, Ralph, 1997 (Box 153, Folder 108)
    - Willson, Rick, 2009 (Box 153, Folder 109)
    - Winogrand, Mark, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 110)
- American Institute of Certified Planners (AICP) Files
  - Photos of the Fellows of the American Institute of Certified Planners (FAICP) Induction Ceremony, 1999-2001 (Box 134)
  - Nominations for FAICP (1), 2008 (Box 135)
  - Nominations for FAICP (2), 2008 (Box 136)
  - AICP College of Fellows Ceremony Program, 1999-2012 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - AICP Fellows Task Force, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
  - FAICP Membership Requirements and Examinations (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster (Handwritten Alphabetical), 1978 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 1980 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 1981 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 1983 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 1985-1986 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 1994-1995 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 2000 (Box 33)
  - AICP Member Roster, 2001 (Box 33)